Based on true events
Septembers of Shiraz is a drama, thriller film directed by Wayne Blair.
In this adaptation of the critically acclaimed debut novel by Iranian American author Dalia Sofer, a
secular Jewish family is caught up in the maelstrom of the 1979 Iranian Revolution.
Isaac, played by Adrien Brody.
Farnez, played by Salma Hayek Pinault.
Farideh, played by Gabriella Wright.
Habibeh, played by Shohreh Aghdashloo.
Komiteh Member, played by Bashar Rahal.
Mohsen, played by Alon Aboutboul.
Septembers of Shiraz is a 2015 American drama film directed
by Wayne Blair and written by Hanna Weg.
It is based on the 2007 novel The Septembers of Shiraz by Dalia Sofer.
The film stars Adrien Brody, Salma Hayek, Shohreh Aghdashloo,
Anthony Azizi, Bashar Rahal and Alon Aboutboul.
The film was released on June 24, 2016, by Momentum Pictures.
The film explores themes of teheran (tehran), iran, based on true
story, jewish family, fleeing, iranian revolution.
The tone is emotional and intense.